# AHMAD HAIKAL IHSAN

089627430341 | a.halkalihsan@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/ahmadhaikalihsan|

Palembang, Indonesia

A bachelor degree of Manajemen Informatics from Polytechnic of Sriwjaya State. Experienced as a Front-End Developer who works with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js and Node.js. Currently working as a Front-End Developer and also attending Full-Stack Web Developer bootcamp program for deepening skills in Web Developer. A detail-oriented individual who is eager for a full-time opportunity in Full-Stack Web Development.

#### **Work Experience**

#### PT. Insurance Tech - Tangerang, Indonesia

Jan, 2022 - Jul, 2022

Full-Stack Developer Intern

- Created the programs and code that power the website's databases, server, and any other applications it could contain
- Developed the actions on a website or web applications using programming languages such as Python, PHP, Ruby etc
- Defined and applied rules to incorporate billions of rows of data from third party data feeds directly into the product back-end

## **Project Experiences**

Film Web - Harisenin Project

Aug, 2022 - Present

Front-End Developer

- Developing a film website using HTML, CSS and Javascript with the team
- Creating a film website for final project

#### Technology Web - Self Project

Jan, 2022 - Jul, 2022

Full-Stack Developer

- Involved with bug fixing on functionality, performance and designing issues with JavaScript, HTML and CSS
- Developed back-end log in Java to be implemented in Indonesia that was used to potential users

### **Organization Experiences**

The Local Concert - Bandung, Indonesia

Jan, 2022 - Feb, 2023

Web Developer Staff

- Designed and Developed The Local Concert web, including its ticketing system and automated internal processes, increasing efficiency by 27%
- Helped The Local Concert to increase site traffic and improve page ranking by reworking website structure and performing SEO and SEM practice

## **Education Level**

### Polytechnic of Sriwijaya State - Palembang, Indonesia

2019 - 2023

Bachelor Degree of Management of Informatics, 3.60/4.00 (Cumlaude)

- Thesis: Application of Weighted Moving Average (WMA) Method In Prediction Application for Timber Production Management At Indonesia Fibreboard Industry Company
- Relevant Course Works: Database, Web Development, System, HTML, and JavaScript

### **Courses, Training and Certifications**

Harisenin.com - Jakarta, Indonesia

SSS

Nov, 2023 - Feb, 2022

Full Stack Developer Bootcamp, 3.54/4.00

- Final Project: Designed and developed a website for an insurance company, Insurance Technology, within three months
- Relevant Course works: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React Native and Node.js
- Certificate:

#### **Skills**

Technical skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Node.js, React Native, Python, PHP, Figma

Soft skills: Problem Solving, Time Management, Orientation to Detail, Analytical Thinking and Teamwork

Languages: Indonesian (Native), English (Intermediate)